到底发生了什么
What is going on over there?
-一点小伤病  -特技出了点小差错
- It's a minor injury issue. - A stunt went slightly awry.
校对     小酸奶
又来
Again?
还有一位主演有些勒伤
And one of our stars got a little strangled.
-什么  -一点点勒伤
- What? - Just a little strangled.
时间轴     奶粉袋
最小程度的勒伤
Like, the minimum amount of strangled.
现在都没事了  就像从未发生过
Everyone's fine now. It's like it didn't even happen.
后期     吉吉
-除了  -除了什么
- Except... - Except what?
有些剧组人员可能拍了事故视频
Some crew members might have taken some video of the incident
总监     小酸奶
随时可能泄露给媒体
that could leak to the press at any moment.
但没有别的了
But that's it!
好吧  我要终止制作
Okay, I'm pulling the plug.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b b b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
-什么  -不要
- What? - No!
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
┌
┐
└
┘
风险太大了  我们得及时止损
It's too dangerous! We gotta cut our losses.
止损  《菲尔伯特》可是大热剧
Cut your losses? Philbert is a monster hit!
我们让你的网站名声大振  小子
We put your site on the map, boy-o,